Thank you.
どう も
Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
かわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Your smile is really nice.
笑顔めっちゃいいっすね
I see.
なるほどね
Are you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張してるかな?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張してる
It makes me nervous.
緊張するよね
I wish there was a handsome guy like this nearby.
こんだけイケメンが近くにいたらね
That's right, after all.
そうっすよね、やっぱり
I agree.
そうですね
How old are you now?
今ってさ、年齢いくつぐらいなんですか?
I'm 19 now.
今19です
Ah, you're young.
あ、若いっすよね
It definitely gives off a youthful feeling.
やっぱ若さ特有の感じ出てるよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This youth is truly a treasure.
この若さはね、本当に宝ですから
yes.
はい
I see.
なるほどね
Then I thought I'd like to ask you some questions.
そしたら僕ちょっといろいろ質問していきたいなと思ったんです
But right now, with my part-time job,
けど、 今なんかさ、バイトとかさ、
What are you doing?
何もやってるの?
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトとかしたりしてるの?
I'm currently working at Mos Burger.
今モスバーガーで働いてます
Oh, Mos Burger?
あ、モスバーガー?
Yeah.
うん
Why did you decide to do it?
なんでやろうと思ったの?
I like hamburgers.
ハンバーガー好きで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Surprisingly, I like junk.
意外にジャンクのもの好きなんだ
So?
それで?
Yes, Mos Burger.
そう、モスバーガー
Mac seems to be having a hard time, so Moss is calming down a bit.
なんかマック大変そうだから、ちょっとモス落ち着いてるから、
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
Shall we have a burger?
バーガーにしようかな
Well, there are a lot of things like Macs.
そのさ、マックとかさ、いろいろあるじゃん
What do you like most?
どこが一番好きなの?
I like moss.
モスが好き
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうなんだ
It's the most delicious.
一番おいしいよね
You're doing a great job.
すげーちゃんとしてるよね
Yes, because I'm doing it right.
そう、ちゃんとしてるから
After all, it's made from scratch, after you order it, right?
あれってさ、やっぱ1からさ、注文してから作るんでしょ?
Yes, we make it every time you order.
そう、 注 文 してから毎回作るから、
It will take a while, but
ちょっと時間かかっちゃうんですけど、
It's freshly made, so it's hot and delicious.
出来立てだから熱くておいしい
Ah, so have you ever done anything like that cooking process?
あー、じゃあその料理工程みたいなのもやったことあるの?
I also do the cooking process from time to time.
料理工程もちょくちょくやってますよ
So what's your favorite menu item?
じゃあ自分の一番好きなメニューは?
Spicy Mos Burger.
スパイシーモスバーガーです
I've come across something pretty major.
結構メジャーなやつきたね
Ah, that's what it feels like.
あ、ああいう感じ
Well, I also like things that are a little spicy.
じゃあちょっと辛いものとかも好きなんだ
It's spicy, and it has something called jalapeno in it.
辛いの、なんかハラペーニョっていうのが入ってて、
Jalapenos are really delicious.
ハラペーニョがめちゃめちゃおいしいんですよ
Surprisingly, I often eat junk food.
意外にじゃあジャンクのもの食べたりするんだね
Actually, are you going to meet your boyfriend now?
実はさ、今さ、彼さんとかいたりするのかな?
No, I'm not there right now.
いや、今はいないです
Actually, are you okay with going on a date or having a Mos Burger?
実はさ、デートとかさ、そういうモスバーガーとかでも平気?
It's totally fine.
全然平気
I'm totally fine with the size.
サイズとかでも全然平気
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうなんだ
I feel like we should just have fun together.
一緒にいて楽しければいいって感じなんだ
He's such a nice kid.
めちゃくちゃいい子ですね
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうなんですね
I see.
なるほど
Eh, what do you think?
え、どうですか?
Is your part-time job fun?
バイト楽しいかな?
It's fun.
楽しいです
I mean, don't you ever meet each other at part-time jobs or something?
なんかさ、バイトとかでさ、出会ったりしないの?
Did you meet?
出会ったり?
Encounter, encounter.
出会い、出会い
Ah, an encounter?
あ、出会い?
encounter.
出会い
But since there are a lot of college students, there are a lot of people around the same age,
でも、大学生多いから、同い年ぐらいの人たち多いから、
There may be many encounters.
結構出会いは多いかもしれない
But everyone has a girlfriend, so
でも、みんな彼女がいたりするから、
I guess not much.
あんまりないかな
I see.
なるほどね
But have you ever been approached?
でも、言い寄られたりしたことあるでしょ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
How do you feel approached?
どういう感じで言い寄られんの?
Oh, I wonder what it is, they asked me to go home with them.
え、なんだろう、一緒に帰ろうって言われて、
Let's go home together.
一緒に帰ろうと
It gives off a very nostalgic atmosphere.
なんかすごい懐かしい雰囲気になるやつだね
So, when we returned together?
で、一緒に帰ったときに?
We went home together and held hands a little more.
一緒に帰って、もうちょっと手繋いできたりとか
ah.
あー
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Sometimes I get invited to a hotel as if I'm not going to the hotel again.
普通にホテルこれから行かないみたいな感じで誘われたりも
be.
ある
Suddenly?
急 に?
Suddenly.
急に
Takeout?
テイクアウト?
yes.
そう
Am I going to get taken out?
自分、テイクアウトされちゃうの?
Yeah.
うん
I see.
なるほどね
Well, have you ever had takeout?
え、テイクアウトされたりはしたことあるのかな?
Yeah, a little bit.
うん、ちょっとね
There is.
ありますよ
Well, really, that's what makes it spicy.
それね、本当、それこそスパイシーだね
hey.
ね
I see.
なるほどね
yes.
はい
So, why, when I said let's go home together,
それでさ、なんでさ、一緒に帰ろうって言ったときさ、
I could have refused.
断ることもできたわけじゃん
Yeah, well, I wanted to have someone to go home with.
うん、まあ別に、帰る人がいたかったし
I felt like I should just go home.
帰るだけやったらいいかな、みたいな
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
After all, people like that, even when they're at their best, they're a little...
やっぱそういう人ってさ、思いっきりいるときもちょっとさ、
Do they talk to each other from a distance?
距離近く話してきたりとかするのかな?
Yes, I do.
うん、するするする
ah.
あー
So, are you sure you'll find out?
それさ、やっぱバレたりすんの?
Well, at work, etc.
そのさ、職場とかでさ
I'm desperately trying not to get caught.
バレないように、必死にもう
Are you confident that you won't be found out?
バレてない自信はある?
I wonder what's going on, is it obvious?
どうなんだろう、バレてるのかな?
But you know when it's someone else,
でも、他の人のときわかるでしょ、
perhaps.
多分
Even with other people.
他の人のときもね
Yeah, if other people felt like that,
うん、他の人がさ、そういう感じになってたら、
I think these two are kind of nice.
この2人ちょっといい感じだなとかさ
Ah, well, it's definitely the atmosphere.
あー、まあ確かに雰囲気で
You know what?
わかるでしょ
I understand.
わかりますね
Did that get across to you?
それ、伝わったりしてたかな?
Maybe.
もしかしたらね
surely.
確 かに
Is it being passed down?
伝 わってるのかな?
Maybe there was,
もしかしたらあったかもしれない、
That's what it is.
そういうのは
I see.
なるほどね
Well, with the person who returned,
そのさ、一緒にさ、帰った人とさ、
The person when I was taken out,
自分がテイクアウトされたときの人、
Who are you with?
一緒の人?
Ah, together, together.
あ、一緒一緒一緒
We're together.
一緒なんだ
So why did that person...
それでさ、なんでその人が、まあね、
Did it look good?
見た目が良かったの?
Was that person good on the inside?
その人の中身が良かったの?
At that time, I guess it's how it looks.
そのときは見た目かな
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
Oh, that was cool.
あ、かっこよかったんだ
Yeah, if you're not cool, you might not be able to do that.
うん、かっこよくないと、そういうことできないかも
Ah, that's honest.
あ、正直だね
Honest and honest.
正直正直
Huh, what kind of type is it?
え、どういう系がタイプなんすか?
Well, if I were to talk about celebrities, it would be Koibito Nagase from King & Prince.
えっと、芸能人で言ったら、キング&プリンスの長瀬恋人くん
That's what I mean.
っていう
Ah, he's handsome.
あ、 イケメンだね
I like people who are a little refreshing.
ちょっと爽やかな人が好きなんですね
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好き
I see.
なるほど
What about personality?
性格とかは?
As for my personality, I like people who are dependable.
性格は、頼りがいのある人が好きです
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
I feel like I can rely on it.
頼りがいがある感じね
Does it include strong people or something like that?
力持ちとかそういうのも入ってるのかな?
Well, yeah.
まあ、うん
character?
性格?
I want someone who can help me when I'm in trouble.
困ってるときに助けてくれたりする人がいいかな
Well, I guess he's a man who can afford it.
まあね、余裕がある男ってことかな?
Do you ever ask men for fashion?
なんか男の人にさ、ファッションとか求めたりする?
Do you even like this kind of fashion?
こういうファッションが好きとかあったりするのかな?
I don't really look for that much, but I guess I don't look too much for looks.
特にそんなに求めないけど、外見にはそんなに求めないかな
Well, the person I choose as my boyfriend isn't all that cool.
なんか、彼氏にする人は一回そんなにかっこよくないけど
But when I say my favorite face, I think it's Koi Nagase.
でも好きな顔って言ったら、長瀬恋っていう感じ
I see.
なるほどね
Should I recruit?
募集しておく?
With this.
これで
Oh, I'm recruiting.
あ、募集してます
Nagase Koi-kun is a handsome guy, and I feel like he's reliable.
長瀬恋くんにのイケメン、頼りがいがある感じね
yes.
はい
I see.
なるほどね
Well, if you're like that, after all,
まあやっぱ、そういう感じの人だとね、
You seem popular, don't you?
モテそうだよね
Well, today, let's ask some more questions like this.
そしたらまあ、ちょっと今日ね、もうちょっとこういった質問を
I'm going to do it, but...
して いくんですけど、 そのさ、
A man who was taken out?
テイクアウトされた、男性?
Yeah.
うん
Honestly, how was it?
ぶっちゃけどうでした?
Well, it was cool, so I had fun.
まあでも、かっこよかったから、楽しかった
How did it all turn out?
どういう流れでやっぱなったの?
That's what it is.
そういうのはさ
Well, it was cold when we went home together.
なんかね、その一緒に帰ってて、寒かったんですよ、
That day.
その日
Let's buy a warm drink and go to the park.
ちょっと暖かい飲み物でも買って公園行こうよ、
Something like that.
みたいな感じ
First time together in the park?
最初に公園で一緒に?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It was night in the park, so there was no one there.
公園で夜だったから、誰もいないから、
We were flirting a little bit.
ちょっとなんかイチャイチャしてて
Well, that was too beautiful.
まあそれ、出来れいすぎたね
I thought it was good from the beginning,
最初からもういいなって思ってたんだ、
myself.
自分が
No, the other side set up a little trick,
いや、向こうがちょっと仕掛けてきたから、
I won't flirt with you like that,
私からはそんななんかイチャイチャはしないから、
When the other side becomes a little weak,
向こうがちょっと程度してきたら、
I'll give it all back.
全部それ返すっていう
I see.
なるほどね
Don't you give things to someone you love?
好きになった人にはさ、自分から出したりしないの?
Something like this, it brings the sense of distance closer.
そのなんかこう、距離感近づけるとかさ、
There will be more body touching.
ボディータッチ増えるとかさ
No, no, I think if I get closer to you, I'll probably end up hating you.
いや いや、 だ って 距離感近づけたら逆に嫌われちゃいそう
That's why I won't do anything from here on out.
だから、 もうこっちからは全然何もしないから
I'd like to make a little appeal.
もうなんか、ちょっとアピールするけど
What kind of appeal?
どういうアピールを?
Well, I'll at least invite you to dinner,
まあ、ご飯誘うぐらいはするけど、
For example, persistently LINE,
例えばしつこくLINEするとか、
Before making a phone call or anything like that, I'll make sure we're close enough together.
電話かけるとかそういうのは、ちゃんと距離を縮めてからやる
Ah, I want you to take steps.
あ、段階を踏んでほしいってことなんだ
Yes, you have to go through the steps.
そう、段階を踏んでからじゃないと、
The other person will probably think you're being too persistent.
多分向こうもしつこって思っちゃうから
So, you don't want to be invited out for the first meal after all?
じゃあ、1回目のご飯で誘われるのはやっぱり嫌だ?
I don't mind if it's someone I like,
全然、好きな相手だったらいいけど、
But if I did that on my first meal,
でも1回目のご飯でそれしちゃったら、
I'm afraid that's the only way I'll be able to see it.
それでしか見られなくなっちゃいそうで怖い
I see, I wonder if you have that kind of experience.
なるほど、そういう経験あるのかな、
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほどね
I see.
なるほどね
Yes, yes, I see.
はいはいはい、なるほど
Well, you know, it also means playing against yourself a little bit.
まあ、でもね、ちょっと自分を対戦するって意味でもね、
It's important, isn't it?
大切ですよね
So, would it be better to have lunch for the first time?
じゃあ1回目、ランチとかの方がいいのかな?
I'd rather have lunch.
ランチとかの方がいいですね
It's like a date spot or something.
なんかさ、デートスポットとかでさ、
Is there any place you would like to go?
どっか行ってみたいとことかあったりするの?
Enoshima.
江ノ島
Will there be a Risso date?
リソーのデートとかあったりする?
I want to go to Enoshima.
江ノ島に行きたいです
Enoshima?
江ノ島?
There's the ocean, and I want to eat whitebait.
海があるし、あとシラスを食べたい
Oh, raw whitebait?
あ、生シラスの?
yes.
そう
Dance and eat.
踊り食い
Yes, I want to eat it.
うん、食べたい
It's so bitter.
渋いっすね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It sure looks interesting.
確かに、面白そうだよね
For some reason, I like fish more than meat.
なんか、お肉よりも魚の方が好きだから
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
So it's silence.
だからサイレンスね
Yeah.
うん
It's healthy.
ヘ ルシーですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I see.
なるほどね
Enoshima.
江ノ島
Drive date.
ドライブデート
I want you to take me on a drive date.
ドライブデート連れて欲しいです、
I'd love to.
是非
I see.
なるほどね
Do you look cool driving?
やっぱドライブしてる姿、かっこよく見えるの?
It looks cool, and I think it's especially cool when you look at it from next to you.
かっこよく見える、隣から見てると特にかっこいいなって思
I'm here.
います
Well, what do you think is cool?
それは さ、どこを見てかっこいいと思うの?
profile?
横顔?
The side profile, the way he's driving, etc.
横顔とか、運転してる姿とか
So, while listening to music together, we looked at the sea.
で、一緒に音楽聴きながら、海を眺めて
Oh, it feels like summer.
おー、なんか夏っぽいっすね
It's the best, isn't it?
最高ですよね
Yes Yes Yes.
はい はい はい
nice.
いいね
That kind of date, have you gone on a date recently?
そういうデートね、ちょっと最近デートはしたかな?
I haven't been on a date recently.
最近デートはしてない
Well, it's difficult.
まあね、難しいよね
Quite a few encounters.
なかなかね、ちょっと出会いがね
An encounter.
出会いがね
Do you like frequency?
結構頻度が好きですか?
Hmm, but if it's with someone you like,
うーん、でも好きな人とだったら、
It could be fun anywhere.
どこでも楽しいかもしれない
Whether it's a date at home or going out somewhere,
お家デートでも、外にどっか出かけるとかでも、
It's fun either way.
どっちでも楽しい
Well, that's true, that's for sure.
まあそうだよね、確かにね
If you're with someone you like.
好きな人と一緒ならね
Ah, that's good.
あー、いいっすね
It would be nice if you could find someone like that.
ちょっとね、そういう人ね、見つかるといいっすよね
Yes, I'll try my best.
はい、ちょっと頑張ります
Well, for those who got taken out...
じゃあ ちょっと、テイクアウトされちゃった人とかは、
Is it someone you're dating?
付き合ってる人かな?
We're not dating.
付き合ってない
There's a girlfriend on the other side too.
向こうにも彼女がいて
Did you notice that before then?
それはその前に気づいちゃったの?
As long as you know.
知ってる上で
Ah, I know that.
あー、知ってる上だね
She's a bad woman.
彼 女は悪い女なんで
Ah, it's just that kind of time.
あー、ちょっとね、そういう時期ばったんだね
Yeah, a little bit.
うん、ちょっとね
I see.
なるほどね
Did that last for a long time?
それ結構続いたんですか?
No, it's just one night.
いや、ワンナイトだけですね
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
Is there any standard for continuing one night?
ワンナイトと続く基準って何かあったりするの?
That's right, hmm, what do I think?
そうだな、うーん、私、どうだろう
I don't need it to be a one-night stand at all,
私は全然ワンナイトじゃなくてもいいんだけど、
I guess the other person felt a little guilty after all.
向こうがやっぱちょっと罪悪感感じたのか、
I feel like I should stop.
なんかもうやめようみたいな
Ah, but most of the time, after all, there are a lot of patterns when it comes to boyfriends.
あー、でも大抵さ、やっぱさ、彼氏にするパターンみたいなのが多
That's not true.
い わけじゃん
Hey, I love you.
ね え、好きだよって
Or maybe I'll invite you to pop.
それかポップに誘うかみたいなさ、
It's kind of like one or the other.
どっちかみたいな感じじゃん
That's how I started feeling like a boyfriend.
それが、彼氏っぽい感じにきた感じなんだ
I was like, ``I love you.''
好きだよみたいな感じにきたんだ
Hmm, no, I felt like it was just my body.
うーん、いやもう完全に体だけだなっていう感じた
That's how I felt, I see.
そう感じたんだ、なるほどね
That was a little sad, you know.
ちょっとそれ悲しかったね、それはね
It's a bit of a shame because it was cool.
ちょっとね、かっこよかったから残念だった
Well, it might be a good idea if it's cool after all.
まあね、やっぱかっこいいならではってあるかもしれないね
I see.
なるほどね
Are there any other positions that make you excited?
他にさ、興奮した位置とかあったりするのか?
Hmm, I guess there's something a little masochistic about me.
うーん、やっぱちょっとMなとこがあるんで
Ah, I see, it's M.
あ、そうなんすか、Mなの
Yes, that's why I was strangled, etc.
そう、だから首しめられたりとか、
I also quite like Nebaku.
あとは寝爆とか結構好きです
I like sleeping bombs.
寝爆好きなんだ
寝爆好き
Is it because it hits the back?
奥に当たるからってこと?
You're going to be climbed on top and from behind, right?
上から後ろから乗っかられるじゃないですか、
That feeling of not being able to move somehow tickles my M heart.
それでなんか動けない感じがなんかちょっとM心をくすぐられる
Or rather?
っていう か
So you're pretty M, really.
じゃあ結構Mなんだね、本当にね
Hey, have you ever had sex in unusual places?
なんかさ、変わったところでエッチしたりとかしたことあるの
kana?
かな?
I've done this before in a park toilet.
公 園のトイレでしたことはあります
Is it a big barrier-free place?
それはバリアフリーのデカいところ?
Oh yeah, it's a big place.
あ、そうそう、大きいところで
But at night, in the middle of the night.
でも夜、夜中とかとか
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
In such a place, if you speak out loud, it will echo outside.
そういうとこでするとなんかね、声出したらあんま外に響いちゃう
Because I have to keep my voice down,
から、 声押さえなきゃいけないから、
I was a little nervous about that.
そこはちょっとね、ドキドキしました
Well, that actually got me excited.
じゃあそれが逆に興奮したんだ
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
It's quite naughty, surprisingly.
結構エッチだね、意外にね
It feels like cleaning.
清掃な感じなのにね
I see.
なるほど ね
Wait, do you masturbate or something?
え、オナニーとかしたりするのかな?
Ah, I will.
あ、します
Oh, I'll do it.
あ、するんだ
Is that a hand?
それは手ですか?
Is it a toy?
おもちゃですか?
Sometimes I use toys.
おもちゃ使うときもあります
Oh, I'm using toys.
あ、おもちゃ使うんだ
So I have my own toy.
じゃあ自分のおもちゃ持ってるんだ
I have it.
持ってます
Is that a vibe?
それはバイブですか?
Electric mass?
電マスか?
It's a vibe.
バイブですね
Ah, it's a vibe.
あ、バイブなんだね
I see.
なるほどね
Isn't that what you do when you're horny?
それさ、ムラムラしたときにするわけじゃないですか?
When do you feel horny?
それはどういうときにムラムラしたりするのかな?
I was lying around at home alone, looking at photos of people I like,
一人で、家でコロコロしてて、 好きな人の写真とか見てて、
I'm getting horny.
ムラムラしてきますね
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうなんだ
Then, it's like imagining having sex with that person.
じゃあ、その人とエッチしてるのを想像しながらする感じなんだ
So, should I add Nebak?
で、ネバック入れるのかな?
Nevak.
ネバックね
I see.
なるほどね
Well then, it's pretty naughty.
じゃあ、結構エッチですね
You should be grateful.
感謝したほうがいいね
Today, a handsome and smooth-looking man is coming.
今日はね、 さらやか系の イケメンの人が来てます
Yes, I understand.
はい、分かりました
I'm going to prepare that person, so please give me a lot of advice.
その人準備するんで、 たくさんいちめてもらってください
Understood.
分かりました
Did you feel a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張溶けたかな?
a bit.
少し
It melted a little.
ちょっと溶けました
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Well, let's get it ready for takeout.
じゃあ、テイクアウトする準備をしておいてもらいましょう
Please take it alone.
一人でもらって、お願いします
Thank you.
どう も
People say I'm Mr. Refreshing.
ミスターさわやかなんて言われますけど
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
Doesn't it look like that at all?
まったくそんな風に見えないですか?
But it seems a little refreshing.
でも、ちょっとさわやかっぽい
Do you like hamburgers?
ハンバーガーが好きなんですか?
I like hamburgers.
ハンバーガー好きです
Do you like hamburgers?
ハンバーガー好きですか?
Hamburgers, yes.
ハンバーガー、そうですね
It's Boumos Burger.
ボウモスバーガーなんですね
Bow Mos Burger.
ボウモスバーガー
I see.
なるほど
I'm a Bow and Santeore fan.
僕 はボウ、 サンテオレ派なんですけど
What is Santeore?
サンテオレってなんですか?
I don't know what Santeore is.
サンテオレって知らないですから
There is such a hamburger.
そういうハンバーガーがあるんです
I only eat fish burgers there.
そこのフィッシュバーガーしか食わないです
Fish burgers can be found everywhere.
フィッシュバーガーって、 どこにでもありますよね
Is that the most delicious?
そこが一番おいしいんですか?
No, Mos Burger is more delicious.
いや、モスバーガーのほうがおいしいです
After all.
結局ね
But yeah, that's true.
でもまあ、そうですね
Will I only eat Santeole?
サンテオレしか食べかないでしょうか
Do you like fish burgers?
フィッシュバーガー好きなんですか?
Do you like fish?
魚とか好きなんですか?
Well, I like fish.
そうですね、魚好きですね
Do you like fish?
魚好きみたいなの?
I like seafood.
海鮮好きです
So to Enoshima?
それで江の島に?
I wanted to go to Enoshima.
江の島に行きたいなと思って
That's right.
そうですよね
It's like I want to go on a live date.
ライブデートしたいみたいな
So, would you like to go with me next time?
じゃあ、今度僕と行きますか?
Will you go?
行ってくれますか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
You look completely happy now.
完全にはもう嬉しそうになりますね
I'm really happy, I'm happy.
本当に嬉しい、嬉しい
Oh, is that so?
ああ、そうですか
Later if you like.
もしよかったら後日
Let's go.
行きましょう
Is this leather?
これ皮なんですか?
Yes, it's leather.
そう、レザーになってて
Isn't it cold?
寒くないですか?
It's a little cold today, isn't it?
今日ちょっと寒いですよね
Did you go with this?
これで行きました?
I went with this.
これで行きました
It's not cold, is it?
寒くないんじゃない?
It was a bit cold.
ちょっと寒かったです
Was it a bit cold?
ちょっと寒かった?
It's mass play, isn't it?
マスフレそうですね
Massage is wonderful.
マスフレ素敵です
thank you.
ありがとうございます
not at all.
全然
We also have a comb.
僕らしてもってくしがいますね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I don't like this kind of thing.
こういうの好きじゃないですね
I don't think I would try to do this myself.
自分でこうしようとは思わないですね
This is not the case.
こうなんないですね
That's nice.
いいですね
It's cute.
可愛いですね
I'm hungry.
お腹すいた
It's really good.
め ちゃくちゃいいですね
I'm hungry.
お腹すいた